safedownloadsrus148.com 2015-09-14

# Privacy Policy

##  PRIVACY POLICY

Downloadious takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Downloadious's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Downloadious receives, collects and uses information in connection with our website and software provided on the website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site"). 

###  Collection and Use of Information

Downloadious does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). 

Downloadious may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on Downloadious's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other customer service purposes. Downloadious's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information. 

Downloadious may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Downloadious collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Downloadious will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users. 

###  Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Downloadious does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Downloadious may disclose your Personal Information if Downloadious believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Downloadious (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Downloadious (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Downloadious services or members of the public. 

###  Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Downloadious website and software and must LEAVE immediately. 

###  Explicit Content

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that Downloadious shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. Downloadious shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable. 

###  Security

Downloadious takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Downloadious cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Downloadious has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. 

###  Changes to Policy

From time to time, Downloadious may revise this Policy. Downloadious will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Downloadious collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. 

### Contact Information

Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy by writing to Downloadious, 6977 Navajo Rd. Suite 186 San Diego, CA 92119, ATTENTION: "Privacy".
